SHERYL MCGLOCHLIN: Hi.
We've added logs, we're going to add a little bit more kindling, and we're going to go ahead and light a match and we're just going to make sure we kind of get this thing going a little bit, and then we'll be able to add more logs as we do this.
So, Oscar, go ahead and light a match and let's see if we can actually make a fire going.
You know there's going to be different weather conditions that play a factor in this also.
If there is a lot of wind, then this shape that I have right now, this container is going to help a lot because wind will blow out your fire faster than anything and you want to make sure that you get that fire started, and that's where the kindling and the newspaper were heading.
Let me going to go ahead and get this match started.
We're going to start it in a couple of different places.
Some people think that they can just keep a fire going with just paper.
But that is not the case.
If you were to just keep fire in there, your fire-- your campfire would go out pretty quick.
So you do want to make sure you've got logs in there and they will start to catch on fire soon.